- What the--
We ain't even--
Hey, man!
- Hey, Alfred!
- Hey, man, I'm gonna need some
cash for this mirror, man.
- Alfred!
- Hey, hello?
Hello?
- Hey, hey, hey!
- Man, I know you hear me
talking to you, man,
I'm speaking English.
- All right, cool.
Let's just keep it
cool, okay, guys?
- Nigga, if you don't
get out of my face....
- Worldstar!
- No, don't do that to us.
- No, no, no, no no.
I think I'm being
more than fair,
calmly asking for
compensation.
So let's go, bro.
- No, y'all staying
broke tonight.
- Well, you trying to get
in the club before 10:45,
which means you trying
to get in before 11:00,
which means you also broke.
Nobody's stunting
on anybody here.
- Ain't no one stunting
on anyone here.
- Bitch, will you please
shut the hell up?
- Don't talk to me like that!
- I'll talk to whoever
however I want,
if you got a problem with it,
we can settle it,
but my car was not
involved, man.
- Hold on, hold on, man, I'm
getting crazy déjà vu right now.
Okay, where's the dog
with the Texas on him?
Oh, there he is.
That's a trip, man.
- Yo, what's your man on?
- Yo, worry about
this mirror, man.
- Just get another mirror.
You Paper Boy.
You rich, right?
- Whoa! Whoa, whoa, whoa.
You Paper Boy?
- You know it.
- Boy, you so
garbage,
that postal mixtape was garbage.
What it was?
Uh, "Mucking."
Mucking--what the hell
is mucking, Paper Boy?
- Man, you know what it is, I
explained in the hood, nigger.
Why we even talking, man?
Why--
Shit, what's going on?
What's good?
- This is definitely
going on Worldstar.
- No it is not!
Stop it.
Nigga, what are you doing?
- Nigga, what are you doing?
- Okay, well, what's up?
Hmm? Yeah.
I got my people waiting
right over there.
Watch out, baby.
What's up?
Let's go!
- Wait.
- This is so weird, man.
[gunshot]
[OJ Da Juiceman's "No Hook"
playing]
*
- * Back at it craftmatic
* All I know is mathematics
* On the stove
cooking chicken *
* Right wrist just did
gymnastics *
* Acrobatic with the whip
* Like Houdini do the magic
* 'Migo bring me kilos
so I bust them squares up *
* Out the plastic,
get in traffic *
* Also to traffic, known
to make that shit happen *
* Got to use the razor 'cause
* The chickens in some
turkey wrapping *
* After 15 years of trapping
* Now young Juice
done started rapping *
* Blowing 93 OG
from Freddy that he sent *
[muffled] * From Cali,
American deli swag *
* 'Cause my pockets
on a Caesar salad *
* Catch your girl
* Then I snatch her
* Fuck her like a jackrabbit
* Sliding in that 50
* Shorties looking like
they tap dancing *
- Oh, my God.
Why are you up?
- I had a weird dream.
I was swimming in this pool,
but it was like the ocean
and I was swimming with the
seaweed, but it wasn't seaweed,
it was, like, hands.
And I was swimming
with this girl.
And she was saying
if the hands grab you,
they pull you down and drown
you, so swim above them.
- Hmm. That's deep.
- I know.
I think it's about society,
'cause, like--
- Who's the girl?
- I don't know.
- What she look like?
- She was fat.
And not interesting.
- Okay.
- You jealous?
- I'm disappointed
in your story,
'cause you're first saying that
she's fat and annoying,
and then you all of a sudden
turn around
and you're making out
with this bitch.
- I never said
we were making out.
- Were you making out?
- Yeah.
Yeah, we were.
- [laughs]
Oh, man.
I know you.
- No, you don't know me.
- Mmm--oh, no.
- What?
- My breath.
- [sniffs]
Oh, I love it.
What is that?
Curry?
Are you kidding me?
- Like a very deep curry?
That is not--that's, like,
some freaky shit.
[giggles]
- Ooh, I like that.
- What are you--
- I love that.
- You're so stupid.
[giggles]
- I don't care.
- Mm.
Tell me you love me.
- [laughs]
- Why did you just laugh?
- 'Cause you always say that,
and I'm always,
like, "of course."
- Then why don't you
just say "I love you"?
- I love you.
- [scoffs]
Uh-oh.
She's awake.
She's gonna kill us all
with her cuteness.
- You remember you have
Lottie tonight, right?
- Hey, there.
Of course I did.
[mouthing] I did not.
- 'Cause I have
parent teacher conferences.
Also, I don't always want
her at your parents' house.
She lives here.
- I promise she won't be
at my parents' house.
I'll pick her up after work.
- And if you're gonna
be staying here,
I'm gonna need
your help with rent.
- I'll get it to you tonight.
What time are you coming back?
- I don't know,
probably like 11:00?
- 11:00?
11:00's a little late.
You, uh, taking the parents
to Magic City's? Follies?
You know, Cheetahs is actually
a better spot for that.
- I have a date.
You're with Daddy tonight.
Mommy's going on a date
with some corny dude.
Yeah, some corny dude.
What?
No, this is a great
environment for you.
- Thank you very much.
You have a nice flight, now.
- Excuse me, sir--
- Fuck off.
- I know, right?
- That was just rude, man.
Hey, yo, Compound was lit
last night.
Man, my cousin had, like eight
bottles up in that bitch.
They fought with, like,
three ho's a piece, my nig.
Shit was crazy.
Hey, we gonna hit $2 Tuesday at
the Ultimate, you want to roll?
Earn.
Hey, yo, Earn.
[chuckles]
Gotti.
[laughs]
How you look when
you high at work.
- Van's dating
other people.
She's gonna kick me
out the house.
I'm also broke
and I can't sign anyone up
'cause I'm not an old lady.
- Can I go to
the Caribbean on this?
- Well, of course
you can, honey.
I'll even give you
an extra flight.
As long as you keep
flirting with me.
- Oh, okay.
- This bitch is amazing.
- That's really rough.
- I don't know,
I would watch.
- That's more rough.
- Hey, yo, you heard that new
Paper Boy mixtape, man?
I heard it's coming out
this Friday, man.
His last one was hot.
- I haven't really been
keeping up, man.
I don't know who that is.
- Man, get out your
little cave, little boy.
Hey, look, check it out,
here go the video right here.
- * Head to Magic City
* And I bet that paper
* Make her strip
* Paper Man, Paper Man
* Catch me in the paper man
* Like "Wall Street Journal"
- Hey, yo,
that's fly, right?
- That's my cousin.
- Damn,
she is thick as fuck.
Is that weird for you?
- No, Paper Boy.
Paper Boy is my cousin.
- That's your cousin, man,
you gonna want to get in there
before he gets signed, man.
Offering that boy
seven M's on the table.
- Is that a real offer?
- That's a real offer,
them real M's.
- All right, man,
I'll catch you later.
- Where you going?
You going to talk to him?
Hey, tell him I said
"what up."
Is that really your cousin in
the video with the big tits?
You don't know Paper Boy.
[laughs]
- Son.
- Hey, Dad.
Where's Mom?
- Hey, Earn.
- Hey, Mom.
How are you?
- Good.
How're you?
- I'm good.
- Good.
You gonna invite me in?
- [chuckles] No.
- Why not?
I can't afford it.
- Come on,
you really think
I'm here for money?
- We do, yes.
I'm looking for Alfred.
Also, could you pick up
Lottie from Kaya's?
I'm getting a job
and Van's on a date.
- You got a job?
- Hey, good for her.
- Yes, I got a job.
And thanks, Mom.
I'm your son, Earn.
I used to live in there
with you, remember?
- Used to?
There was a turd
the size of
my arm waiting for me
when I got home yesterday.
You supposed to be so smart,
you can't remember to flush?
- That wasn't me.
- It was you. I checked.
You better eat something real.
Instead of all them
candies and cookies
and whatever other stuff
was in there.
- Did you break it up
with a stick?
- Alfred's at the
Glenwood apartments.
Love you, son.
["Paper Boy" playing]
- * You flexing
you's a hater boy *
* Paper Boy, Paper Boy
* Always getting paper boy
* If you ain't making money
* Man you ain't
a money maker boy *
* Paper clip, paper clip
* Yeah I need a paper clip
- Hey, is this milk any good?
- What you using it for?
- Drinking.
- Yeah, no, man,
don't use that to drink.
[knock at door]
- Your peephole's for real.
- That's Darius.
- [clears throat]
Cookie?
- Thanks.
So, Zoo Tycoon--
- You want in on Paper Boy.
- What?
No.
- Please, man.
People ain't just nice, Earn.
When was the last time
you were nice to a girl
you weren't trying to smash?
- This morning.
- You talking about your
daughter, man, that's gross.
- No, it'd be gross
if I was trying to smash.
I don't want a handout,
I want to manage you.
- Manage?
You know where the word
"manage" come from?
- "Manus," Latin for hand.
- Probably, but I'm gonna say no
for the purpose of my argument.
"Manage" come from the word
"man," and, uh,
that ain't really
your lane.
- My lane?
- Yeah, man, I need Malcolm.
You too Martin.
You know what they did to him?
They killed him.
- Didn't they kill
Malcolm, too?
- Oh, no, they say that.
But ain't nobody seen
the body since the funeral.
- That's how funerals work.
Alfred, you already
Malcolm, okay?
You have that already.
What you really need
is a silent wild card,
somebody who's about the money,
the opportunity,
who can play both sides
if needed.
- Oh, like Don Lemon.
- Fair point, let me rephrase
what I'm trying to say.
- Oh, wait, wait, wait.
It's 4:30.
- Oh, damn, man, we late.
- No.
- Since when?
- I'm doing business.
- Hey, you want
a manager a rapper,
but you can't do
business hot?
VH1 is hiring interns.
And that sound like a joke,
but they
actually,
they tweeted that
this morning.
- How's Princeton,
by the way?
Still on that year off?
Three years is a long year off.
- I guess.
- I think I know what happened.
- I really think you don't.
Look, man, is there somewhere
we can talk for
real?
'Cause...
I'm sorry,
who is this dude?
- Darius, man.
- Man, I'm fine with talking--
- When you first walked in;
I gave you cookie.
- No, yeah,
I remember who you are.
Look, I'm not
asking for money.
- You should be,
ain't you homeless?
- Not real homeless.
I'm not using a rat
as a phone or something.
- Don't be racist, man.
That make you schizophrenic,
that don't make you homeless.
- Wait, wait,
not if it worked, man.
No, if you could use
a rat as a phone, man,
that'd be genius.
I mean, there's like
five rats
for every one person
in New York alone.
Everybody would have
an affordable phone.
Yeah, man, I mean,
it'd be messy, but...
worth it.
- Is he your manager?
- [sarcastically]
Rappers need managers.
I'm just trying to
get paid right quick.
- Yeah, man, rap is D-E-D.
Ded.
- [giggles]
- This isn't about rap.
If we do this right,
your kids can live good,
my kids can live good,
Darius's kids.
- I can't have kids.
- I'm sure I'll find out why
when the time's right.
- When is an appropriate
time to talk about
my balls getting smashed?
- Right now,
apparently.
Look, I'm not dumb.
You're older,
you have no real fan base.
You're not white
and/or selling sex.
- I sell sex, man.
Hey, track 28.
- Yeah.
[smooth hip hop music]
*
- Oh!
- Come on.
- Uh.
- * Hey mucking, mucking
* That's massage and
* Fucking, fucking
See, the concept is a massage--
- I got the concept.
Okay, 28 tracks?
Lot of skits.
I'd cut 'em.
- No, but his is different.
- Yeah, mine are really good.
- I'd still cut 'em.
- Well, you not
my manager, Earn.
- I still know people
at Diamond House.
Promoters.
People who manage big time
artists now, man.
- Oh, boy,
you think you slick.
You coming in here,
acting like you saving me,
when really,
I'm saving you again.
- Nigga, I'm trying
to help you.
- Man, nigga, I ain't
seen or heard from you
since my mom's funeral.
And the first thing
I hear out your mouth
is "let's get rich."
Walk, man.
- What's up, dude?
- Earn?
Yo, what's up, man?
Yo.
- Good.
- Did you just come
from that dumpster?
- No.
How are you?
- Oh, yo,
I'm good, man.
I didn't know
you were in town.
- Uh, yeah,
I've been low-key, man.
- Yo, obviously--
oh, dude, if I knew
you was in town,
I would've hit you up
with this party last night.
Yo, we needed a real DJ.
This dude--well,
he can't spin worth of shit,
but then he goes
and he plays Flo Rida.
- No!
- Back to back.
- So I calmly pull him aside,
I was just like,
"Really, nigga?"
- You actually said that?
- Yeah, man, I had to.
- Cool. You know that song
"Paper Boy"?
- Yeah, "Paper Boy"
by Paper Boy.
Yeah, I've heard it.
Shit's fine.
Dude, the streets love it.
- Y'all should play it.
- Yeah, for real.
- Yeah.
You guys should
really play it.
- Uh, I mean,
KP picks all the music.
- Well, slide it past him.
- I mean, KP will usually
spin some records
for some scratch up top.
- How much?
- Half a stack.
- $500?
Am I buying the station?
- Everything is who you know.
- Then introduce me.
- Yeah, I'm gonna
introduce every dude in Atlanta
with a mixtape in my box.
Come on.
- I'm not every dude.
- Uh, you kind of are.
- Look, I don't have $500.
I make 5.15,
plus commission.
I got to pay rent tonight
and my parents
won't let me in the house.
It's like those drug
commercials,
only not funny.
- Man, you know how
niggas out here are.
I mean, he usually
charges a full safe.
- Then what's in it for you?
Why am I so lucky?
What's your cut?
- Oh, I'm not about that,
I'm too busy, man.
I mean,
it's just business.
You give me the money,
I pass it on to KP.
But you know,
it's probably for the best.
Music business is gross.
All right, man, well, you know,
it was great seeing
ya.
I'm taking over
for Speedy tonight.
All right?
Keep it locked.
What's up, my dudes?
What's up, bro?
- Hey.
Hey.
That guy ever say
nigger around you?
- Yeah, right.
I'd break my foot in his ass.
- Right.
Hey, um...
what's your name?
- Prince, man.
- For real?
- Yeah.
- Hey, how late
are you here tonight?
[hip-hop music playing]
*
- [chuckles]
- What's up, Uncle Riley?
- Hey, what's going on, Al?
- Man, you know.
Hey.
Hey, Auntie.
Oh, hey, Lottie.
Hey, bring Lottie over here,
let me say hey to my cousin.
- That's okay.
She getting a
contact high from here.
- Contact high--
that's that new leather
you smelling.
You smelling it wrong.
- Yeah, well, I'm smelling it
'round your head.
- Say what?
- Hey.
- You got a weird wife,
you know that, huh?
- Hey, um...
hey, look, I know
you don't know me--
my name's Darius.
Um, I was just wondering,
could I measure your tree?
- No, not right now.
- Not right now?
That basically means no, man.
- Look, I got a question.
So Earn want to manage me.
- Really?
- [chuckles]
And I don't trust him,
no offense.
- I understand.
- That's what's messed up.
I don't really think
I know Earn anymore.
[hip-hop music]
Like, what happened
at Princeton?
- I never asked.
He'd tell you before me.
- No.
Earn is good at
keeping his mouth shut.
[muffled hip-hop music playing]
*
- Earn trying like
the rest of us.
But when he wants to do
something, he does it.
On his terms.
[faint pop music]
*
- Your mind's racing.
Tell me, yo.
- I just keep losing.
I mean...
some people just...
supposed to lose?
For balance
in the universe?
I mean...
like, are there just
some people on Earth who...
supposed to be here just to make
it easier for the winners?
Like, really.
- Resistance is a symptom
of the way things are.
Not the way things
necessarily should be.
Actual victory
belongs to things
that simply do not
see failure.
Let the path push you
like a broken branch
in a river's current.
- No, no, I'm not
going out like that,
but thanks
for the advice.
- Bite this sandwich.
- No, I'm good, man.
- Nigga, if you don't bite
this sandwich...
[police siren wailing]
[cell phone rings]
- Hello?
- Hey.
Hey, man,
you hear that?
- Hear what?
- Hey, turn it up, man.
Turn it up.
- Hey, man, tell him
I sketched Uncle Riley's--
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
"Paper Boy," boy!
["Paper Boy" playing]
- Wow.
That was quick.
- Hey, man, look,
you should come down here.
We need to talk right quick.
- Like you would with a manager?
- No, nigga, like I would
with a calm yo ass down!
*
[thunder rumbles]
- This is an exclusive.
WMQG exclusive.
*
- * Paper Boy, Paper Boy
* All about that paper boy
*
- You want some dots?
- * Paper Boy Paper Boy
* Always 'bout that paper boy
* Doin' underground
- Yeah.
*
- [gasps]
[laughs]
- * Then you ain't
a money maker boy *
* Paper clip, paper clip
* Yeah I need a paper clip
* I'm stacking up
this paper man *
* And I can make that paper
- Ah.
You found us.
- Hey, guys.
- Hey.
- 'Sup?
- How'd you get in
the building?
- It's all about who you know.
I knew somebody.
- Yeah, well, I mean,
that was unprofessional.
And KP's pissed.
- Can't be that pissed--
they're playing this
on the radio right now.
Hey, man, this is Dave.
He works at 106.5.
He likes your stuff,
so he's got good taste.
Actually, to a fault.
Yo, tell them that
Flo Rida story.
It's so funny.
Yo, tell them.
- Oh, uh...
yeah, so I was at
a station party.
And, uh, the DJ--
a friend of a friend,
was awful, and, uh...
you know, it's a big event
for the station,
and the party's
going and going
and he's ruining it,
and so then he goes
and he plays Flo Rida
back to back.
I had to go into the booth,
calmly take him aside,
and look him right in the eyes,
and just said,
"Really?"
- * Paper boy, Paper boy
* Watch me blow that paper boy
- I don't know, man,
I like Flo Rida.
I mean, moms need to
enjoy rap, too.
- Yeah, I mean,
that was a wack-ass story, man,
I don't know why he
made me tell that.
- Yeah, I don't know.
- All right, man, well,
it was good to see you, Earn.
It was nice
to meet you guys.
- Later, Dave.
- Say hello to KP for me.
- * Racer X, racer X
* Always racing
through the check *
- Hey.
Hey!
Hey, girl.
This is me on the radio.
- So what, bitch?
- Well, same to you,
stank-ass broad.
Whatever.
- * Paper Boy
* All about that Paper Boy
* I feel you about them zeroes
in kilos *
* See you later boy
- It's a good song, man.
- Kind of hate this song.
What the f--
Really, man?
Hey, man!
Hey!
See, these niggas in the
streets, man, they--
- Don't mess with the money.
- Hey, man!
Hey!
- Alfred!
- Hey, man!
- Goddamn it.
- Hey.
Hey, man, I'm gonna need some
cash for this mirror, man.
Hello? Hello?
- Hey, hey!
- Two lanes of blocked road off
US highway 78 headed westbound.
- Lottie's in her crib,
Earn had some business.
You out of wine.
- The bottle?
Thank you.
- Knocked down a power line
in Northwest Atlanta.
This was the scene
on Mount Paran Road
where a tree fell
on a power line.
At the height of
last night's storms,
more than 27,000 Georgia Power
customers were in the dark.
A shooting tonight
in DeKalb County
Two suspects, rapper Paper Boy,
and his manager, Earn Marks,
are now in custody.
And one apparently wounded
suspect is still at large.
Police are still looking
for the wounded suspect
as well as the assault weapon.
Witnesses say the altercation
started outside
the WETBAR nightclub
over a damaged car.
- Idiot.
- * Paper Boy Paper Boy
- * Really
- * All about that paper boy
- * Paper
* Got 'em till we serve 'em
- * From Cali to Decatur boy
- * Stack it
* Paper Boy Paper Boy
* All about that paper boy
- Yeah *
- * I keep it clean
- * Uh, yeah
- * Paper Boy Paper Boy,
always 'bout that paper boy *
* If you ain't on your grind,
then you flexing *
* You's a hater boy
* Paper Boy Paper Boy
* Always getting paper boy
* If you ain't making money
* Man you ain't
a money maker boy *
* Paper Clip, Paper Clip
* Yeah I need a paper clip
* I'm stacking up
this paper man *
* And I can make that paper
flip *
* That paper flip,
paper flip *
* Watch me make
this paper flip *
* Then head to Magic City
* And I bet that paper
make her strip *
* Paper Man, Paper Man
* Catch me in the paper man
* Like "Wall Street Journal,"
yeah *
* 'Cause I be
gettin' paper man *
* That Paper Man, Paper Man
* Yeah, I'm gettin' paper man
* Uh